<resources>
<string name="app_name">Tour Guide</string>
<string name="testName">Domkyrkan</string>
<string name="testAddress">Biskopsgränd 2, 645 30 Strängnäs</string>
<string name="testPhone">0152 245 00</string>
<string name="testDescription">Bork</string>
<string name="church1Name">Åkers Kyrka</string>
<string name="church1Address">647 50 Åkers Styckebruk</string>
<string name="church1Phone">0159 348 40</string>
<string name="church1Description">Tiny church near Åker. Oddly the priest for Åker lives in Länna, and the priest for Länna lives in Åker.</string>
<string name="church2Name">Strängnäs Cathedral</string>
<string name="church2Address">Gyllenhjelmsgatan 2, 645 30 Strängnäs</string>
<string name="church2Phone">0152 234 00</string>
<string name="church2Description">Cathedral of Strängnäs. Here the great Gustav Vasa was elected king to expel the Danes after the Stockholm Bloodbath. His election is reenacted every summer by proud natives of Strängnäs.</string>
<string name="church3Name">Vansö Kyrka</string>
<string name="church3Address">Vansö Kyrkbacke 1B, 645 92 Strängnäs</string>
<string name="church3Phone">0152 201 29</string>
<string name="church3Description">A small church on Fogdö. The name "Fogdö" means "parish island", but it is actually a peninsula.</string>
<string name="church4Name">Ytterselö Kyrka</string>
<string name="church4Address">Selaön, Strängnäs</string>
<string name="church4Phone"></string>
<string name="church4Description">This beautiful small church is the family church of the Soop aristocratic family. The church served the palace of Mälsåker.</string>
<string name="church5Name">Länna kyrka</string>
<string name="church5Address">Klockargårdsvägen, 645 91 Strängnäs</string>
<string name="church5Phone"></string>
<string name="church5Description">This tiny church in a settlement that does not even qualify as a village actually possesses a wooden statue from medieval times. The statue was one of a pair robbed from Eskilstuna, and was found in the 1970s when it was used as an impromptu goal post for a childrens\' soccer game.</string>
<string name="church6Name">Mariefred Charterhouse</string>
<string name="church6Address">Storgatan 3, 647 30 Mariefred</string>
<string name="church6Phone">0159 104 79</string>
<string name="church6Description">This beautiful church is the highest point of Mariefred, and its hilltop provides a beautiful view of the town and the lake Mälaren.</string>
<string name="palace1Name">Gripsholm Castle</string>
<string name="palace1Address">647 31 Mariefred</string>
<string name="palace1Phone">0159 101 94</string>
<string name="palace1Description">This castle and palace now hosts the Royal Portrait gallery, while also preserving some beautiful renaissance rooms. There are also frequent events with guest speakers and music. The castle is the most beautiful site in the region and should not be missed! Gustav III had a theatre erected in the attic. The site first became a fortification when it was ordered built by Bo Jonsson Grip, a medieval aristocrat who owned more land and wealth than the King. The fields around Mariefred hold medieval tournaments every summer to commemorate this period of local history.</string>
<string name="palace2Name">Mälsåker Palace </string>
<string name="palace2Address">MÄLSÅKERS GODS 4, 645 97 Stallarholmen</string>
<string name="palace2Phone"></string>
<string name="palace2Description">Mälsåker Slott was the home of the Soop family, and a connection with royalty made the building a royal palace rather than an estate. It was originally famous for its beautiful inlaid wooden floors. This was destroyed by the state organ for preservation of antiquities to install their archives, which never took place. It was also famous for the stucco work on the ceiling of the top floor. This was destroyed by Norwegian soldiers during a cold winter in the Second World War, when the soldiers were quartered here and set the building on fire for warmth. The palace has since been used to practise restoration techniques.</string>
<string name="palace3Name">Sundbyholms Slott</string>
<string name="palace3Address">635 08 Eskilstuna</string>
<string name="palace3Phone">016 42 84 00</string>
<string name="palace3Description">Sundbyholm is forever tied to the history of Hertig Karl, a Duke who became king through his struggles to maintain Sweden Swedish rather than accepting a Polish (and therefore Catholic) royal relative assuming the throne. It is now a business for conferences and such. Below the palace is a beautiful garden, a marina, and some of the best local views of lake Mälaren.</string>
<string name="palace4Name">Fiholm Estate</string>
<string name="palace4Address">FIHOLMSBY GÅRD 1, 635 05 Eskilstuna</string>
<string name="palace4Phone"></string>
<string name="palace4Description">Fiholm was erected by the Oxenstierna family, who long served as chancellors of Sweden, most notably Axel Gustavsson Oxenstierna, whose brilliance and cooperation with king Gustav II Adolf turned Sweden into an empire and guarantor of the peace of the Treaty of Westphalia. The palace was built for a scion of the family who grew up spoiled in Germany, and mocked the palace as looking like a "Saxon Stable", for which reason it was never completed. It is privately held, but occasionally holds art exhibitions and musical events.</string>
<string name="palace5Name">Elghammar Palace</string>
<string name="palace5Address">646 96 Björnlunda</string>
<string name="palace5Phone"></string>
<string name="palace5Description">Initially owned by the Kruse family of Elghammar, then Johan Adolf Welander, the existing manor was sold during the year 1807 to Marshall Curt von Stedingk who ordered new constructions in the style of the French Empire. His son died in 1875 and inherited by a daughter, who married the Duke of Otrante. The castle, or Italian villa as the owner, the Duchess Christina d\'Otrante, prefers it to be perceived, is surrounded by forests and a farm.</string>
<string name="nature1Name">Åsa gravfält</string>
<string name="nature1Address">985, 645 96 Stallarholmen</string>
<string name="nature1Description">Bronze age burial site, and also one of the only places in the world where you can find the wild flower "backsippor"</string>
<string name="nature2Name">Sigurdsristningen</string>
<string name="nature2Address">Sundbyholm Ramsund 1, 635 08 Eskilstuna</string>
<string name="nature2Description">The largest rune carving in the world in the side of a hill. The carving shows the entire story of Sigurd Fafnesbane (also known as Siegfried in the Wagner\'s "Ring des Nibelungen". It was commissioned by a viking age woman in memory of her deceased husband.</string>
<string name="nature3Name">Vårfruberga Klosterruin</string>
<string name="nature3Address">Kungsberg, 645 92 Strängnäs</string>
<string name="nature3Description">The ruins of a nunnery by the lake Mälaren. The nunnery lost its funding and fell into disrepair in the wake of Gustav Vasa\'s ascension to the throne. There is a local legend of a monk from the cathedral in Strängnäs visiting his love in the nunnery each night by rowboat from the town.</string>
<string name="food1Name">Formosa</string>
<string name="food1Address">Storgatan 12, 645 30 Strängnäs</string>
<string name="food1Phone">0152 124 66</string>
<string name="food1Description">Chinese restaurant in central Strängnäs. Buffet lunch daily for 75SEK, excellent a la carte options.</string>
<string name="food2Name">Den Vita Elefanten</string>
<string name="food2Address">645 30, Eskilsgatan 2B, 645 30 Strängnäs</string>
<string name="food2Phone">0152 107 04</string>
<string name="food2Description">Originally a Malaysian restaurant, it now has a mostly Thai focus with some Chinese and Malay recipes still on the menu.</string>
<string name="food3Name">UM Thai och Sushi</string>
<string name="food3Address">Eskilstunavägen 18, 645 34 Strängnäs</string>
<string name="food3Phone">0152 100 91</string>
<string name="food3Description">Cheap, simple Thai and Sushi to go.</string>
<string name="food4Name">The Immortal Highlander</string>
<string name="food4Address">Hospitalsgatan 17, 645 30 Strängnäs</string>
<string name="food4Phone">070 442 53 75</string>
<string name="food4Description">A Scottish-style pub opened by a group of friends after a trip to Scotland. Overpriced bar food, good selection of beer and whisky.</string>
</resources>
